[
  {
    "question": "Which Of The Dialog Box Display a Message And a Data Entry Field?",
    "choices": ["Alert()", "Prompt()", "Confirm()", "Msg()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "A Function Associated With An object is Called",
    "choices": ["Function"," Method", "Link", "None"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Event is Used To Check An Empty Text Box",
    "choices": ["Onclick()", "OnFocus()" , "OnBlur()", "None"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Java Script File Has An Extension Of",
    "choices": [".Java",".Js", ".javascript", ".xml"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": " GetMonth() returns The Month as",
    "choices": ["Int", "Float", "Char", "String"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Method Prompt() Contain ........Number of Parameters",
    "choices": ["One", "Two", "Three ", "Zero"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
    "choices": ["Js"," JavaScript", "Script"," Scripting"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Function is Used To Parse a String To Int",
    "choices": ["Integer.Parse", "Int.Parse","Parse.Int"," None"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The Tag is used To Give Heading To The Table",
    "choices": ["Head","Td","Th" ,"Caption"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "IsNaN() Evalutes And Argument To Determine if Given Value",
    "choices": ["Is Not a Null","Is Not a Number","Is Not a New Object","None Of The Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "If Button is clicked .......Event Handler is invoked",
    "choices": ["OnSubmit()","OnLoad()","IsPostBack()"," Onclick()"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  }
]
